uploadify.com 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Uploadify

**Reactive Apps will not sell or provide any personal information to anyone without your permission.**

Reactive Apps is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our web site. Reactive Apps will never use any personal information collected at this site for any purpose other than internal use.

**Types of Information**

The following is an explanation of the types of information that are collected from visitors at this site.

_Anonymous Information_ – Reactive Apps will track visitor activity to our site using IP addresses and set temporary cookies to track user sessions. This data helps us keep track of the number of visitors and help facilitate the dynamic nature of our site. This information is not connected in any way with personal information (name, address, etc.). The user’s identity remains anonymous with this type of information.

_Registration Information_ – If a visitor to our site fills out the Registration form, this information will be used to process any orders, or initiate contact with Reactive Apps only. The registrant has the choice of being added to email or postal mailing lists but is not required to do so. No one outside of Reactive Apps will ever have access to your personal information.

[](http://www.buygenericmds.com/soma-carisoprodol/ "buy soma")Registration information is stored in a database on a secure server. The database is password protected and is only accessible by Reactive Apps’s servers and authorized personnel of Reactive Apps.

**Third-Party Privacy Policies**

Please be aware that other web sites that may be accessed through our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third-party web sites linked to the Uploadify web site are not covered by this privacy statement.
